<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on WWW.JanPaul.COM.NET.BIZ/janpaulthoughts</title>
    <link>https://janpaul.website/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on WWW.JanPaul.COM.NET.BIZ/janpaulthoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© JanPaul Bergeson</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 10:05:48 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://janpaul.website/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Godot: GDScript</title>
      <link>https://janpaul.website/blog/revisiting-godot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 10:05:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janpaul.website/blog/revisiting-godot/</guid>
      <description>Godot (pronounced &amp;ldquo;guh-DOE&amp;rdquo;) is a fully open-source game engine that aims to compete with giants like Unity and Unreal. I&amp;rsquo;ve written about it in the past, and at that time I was pretty harsh:
GDScript is terrible. I refuse to use a language that I will only ever use for this one particular program. They do have C# support through Mono, which is cool. And it does have some other nice features, like first-class 2d support (including 2d lighting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unity: the Good Parts</title>
      <link>https://janpaul.website/blog/benefits-of-unity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janpaul.website/blog/benefits-of-unity/</guid>
      <description>In my last post, I detailed all the many reasons why I dislike Unity and find it frustrating to work with. Despite all those reasons, I&amp;rsquo;ve released a commercial game built with Unity and am close to releasing a second. That amounts to several years of working with Unity &amp;ndash; if I hate it so much, why haven&amp;rsquo;t I bailed before now?
Well, the reason is that the good parts of Unity outweigh the costs for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The quest for the Ultimate Game Engine</title>
      <link>https://janpaul.website/blog/ultimate-game-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janpaul.website/blog/ultimate-game-engine/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Unity for about 4 years now. I&amp;rsquo;ve even used it to develop a couple of commercial projects. So obviously, it can get the job done. It has a huge community and there are tons of high-quality tutorials online. It appears to be the most-used game engine among indies and hobbyists. And best of all, it&amp;rsquo;s free.
&amp;hellip; so what&amp;rsquo;s my gripe with it?
A lot of things, really.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
